http://mindviz.com/privacy.php

Home | Members | Music | Photos | Videos | Chat Rooms | Games | Forums | Blogs | Polls | Groups»
Privacy Policy
MindViz Privacy Policy
The MindViz Network ("MVIZ"),
comprised of the Internet sites mindviz.com,
adlogic.mindviz.com,
mail.mindviz.com,
mvhosted.com,
mvtracker.com,
ai-buddy.com,
poetictimes.com,
awayhunter.com,
profilehunter.com,
poetsbest.com,
awayhell.com,
pokerhell.com,
aimprank.com,
picsfolio.com,
journalhell.com,
mylinkbox.com,
forumhell.com,
audiohell.com,
avatarhell.com,
iconhell.com,
blinkyhell.com,
dollhell.com,
12gracestreet.com,
and metashark.com (the "MVIZ
Sites"), is committed to protecting the privacy of users of the
MVIZ Sites. At MVIZ, we intend to give you as much control as possible
over your personal information, including registration data. As part
of the normal operation of the MVIZ Sites, we collect information from
you. This Privacy Statement describes the information we collect about
you and how that information may be used.
Information Gathered through the MVIZ Sites:
MVIZ will track the domains from which people visit the MVIZ Sites in
order to gain aggregate data that may be analyzed for trends and
statistics. Subject to the provisions of this Privacy Statement, MVIZ
may use accumulated aggregate data for several purposes including, but
not limited to, marketing analysis, evaluation of MVIZ's
services, and business planning.
Currently, MVIZ uses personal information as a basis for notifications
to users, and in order to implement the Terms and Conditions of Use
governing the MVIZ Sites (the "Terms"). Generally, the user
names, email addresses, and any additional information that a user may
choose to post are publicly available on the MVIZ Sites.  When
users voluntarily and publicly disclose personal information that may
contain Registration Data, as defined in the Terms, or otherwise post
personal information in conjunction with content subject to a license,
such personal information necessarily will be disclosed subject to the
terms of the applicable license. An example of such a disclosure
includes, but is not limited to, a user's disclosure of personal
information as part of a message posted to a public message forum.
MVIZ may conduct surveys or other studies of its user base and usage
for marketing and planning purposes. Participation in such surveys is
at the user's option, but MVIZ does reserve the right to conduct
mandatory surveys in the future. With respect to information collected
from such surveys or studies, and in the event that responses are to
be publicly disclosed, users will be notified at the time they take
the survey and MVIZ will disclose only aggregate information regarding
its users and not personal information identifying any specific
individual. Notwithstanding the foregoing, in cases where surveys
allow users to submit written comments, and where MVIZ advises users
of the possibility of such disclosure at the time they take the
survey, MVIZ reserves the right to disclose text information provided
by any user through such a survey, provided that no personal
information identifying that user is disclosed.  Circumstances
under which MVIZ would publicly disclose aggregate information
include, but are not limited to, sharing survey results with the site
population, providing data to MVIZ advertisers on user preferences
and/or demographics, business planning, and publicizing overall usage
data in press communications.
Cookies: MVIZ employs "cookies" to provide users with
tailored information. A "cookie" is an element of data that
a website, when visited by a user, sends to that user's browser
which, in turn, may store that element on the user's hard drive or
memory.  MVIZ uses cookies to better serve users of our MVIZ
Sites; any cookies sent by MVIZ will be marked so that they will be
accessible only by MVIZ Sites subject to this Privacy Statement.
However, at his or her option and at his or her sole expense and
responsibility, any user may block or delete our cookies from his or
her hard drive. However, by disabling cookies, certain site features
and functionality may no longer work properly, or at all.
Other Notification: In order to implement or enforce the Terms,
MVIZ may use user-provided e-mail addresses to contact users on an
individual basis.  At no time, unless such disclosure is required
by law, a governmental agency, or specifically authorized by the user,
will MVIZ disclose individual user personal information to unrelated
third parties that is not publicly available.
Links with other sites
The MVIZ Sites contain links to other websites, whether owned or
controlled by MVIZ affiliates, or unrelated third parties. Please note
that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from those of the
MVIZ Sites. MVIZ is not responsible for the privacy policies and
practices of any linked website. We encourage you to read the privacy
statement of any website you may visit.
3rd Party Advertisers
We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit www.networkadvertising.org.
Choice
"Opt-in" Emails: Users may "opt-in" to
receive site notifications, newsletters, or other information via
email. Users may remove themselves from such services at their
discretion. Any email sent to an "opt-in" list will include
directions for how a user may remove himself or herself from the list,
or a URL where the user may find such directions.
Co-Registration: Users may "opt-in" to
register for or receive offers from third-parties via
the co-registration offers provided within our member registration process.
Users may remove themselves from such services at their
discretion. Any email sent to an "opt-in" list should include
directions for how a user may remove himself or herself from the list,
or a URL where the user may find such directions. Unfortunately these
services are provided by third parties and MVIZ has no control
over those services ( they are not owned or operated by MVIZ ).
Profile Display: In some cases, users' personal information
may be publicly available through a user's profile display. In
such cases, users have the option to opt out of publicly displaying
their personal information, including e-mail addresses.  Users
may also enlist this technique when posting comments on certain MVIZ
Sites.  In cases where site profiles allow users to display
optional information publicly, such entry and display is at the
user's discretion and may be changed at any time by the user.
Email Display: In some cases, users may have the opportunity to
use an MVIZ Site to send electronic mail to another user or email
list. In such cases, a user's valid email address and real name
will be included with such messages. In order to prevent abuse, users
may not opt-out of such a display, but may choose to refrain from
using such MVIZ Site to transmit an email message.
Access
On certain MVIZ Sites, users can view their data on their personal
profile page. When technically feasible, users are permitted to update
their personal information directly through MVIZ. When such updating
service is not technically feasible, MVIZ will make reasonable efforts
to assist users in updating their personal information.
Security
To secure site integrity, MVIZ employs measures, including but not
limited to security audits, use of encryption tools and software, and
other reasonable security measures and procedures.
Internal access to users' private and nonpublic personal
information is restricted to site administrators and individuals on a
need-to-know basis.
Enforcement
In the event that MVIZ becomes aware that site security is compromised
or nonpublic user information has been disclosed to unrelated third
parties as a result of external activity, including but not limited to
external security attacks, MVIZ shall take reasonable measures which
it deems appropriate, including but not limited to internal
investigation and reporting, and notification to and cooperation with
law enforcement authorities, notwithstanding other provisions of this
Privacy Statement.
If MVIZ becomes aware that a user's personal information provided
to MVIZ has been disclosed in a manner not in accordance with this
Privacy Statement, MVIZ shall make reasonable efforts to notify the
affected user, as soon as reasonably possible and as permitted by law,
of what information has been disclosed, to the extent that MVIZ knows
this information.
Updates to the Privacy Statement
To update the Privacy Statement, we will post both the changed version
and its effective date at http://mindviz.com/privacy.php.
No Guarantees For Factors Beyond MVIZ's Control
While this Privacy Statement expresses MVIZ's standards for
maintenance of private data, it is not in a position to guarantee that
the standards will always be met. There may be factors beyond
MVIZ's control (e.g., "script kiddies", "crackers and other malcontents") that may result in
disclosure of data. As a consequence, MVIZ disclaims any warranties or
representations relating to maintenance or nondisclosure of private
information.
Last modified: October 1st, 2004
privacy   terms©
MindViz
